4webhelp.net 2014-06-30

# 4WebHelp - Privacy Statement

## General Privacy Statement

4WebHelp.net has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: 4WebHelp.net. 

## IP Address

An IP (Internet Protocol) address is a unique identifier for a computer on a particular network; including the Internet. When you log on to the Internet, your computer is issued with an IP address. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, for security purposes and to administer our website. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. 

## Cookies

The main purpose of cookies is to identify Internet users and possibly prepare customized web content for them. We use cookies to enable functionality of our message boards.

## Links to other sites

This site contains links to other sites. 4WebHelp.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

## Public Forums

This site makes chat rooms and forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. These forums are not monitored on a 24/7 basis, but if you feel that an item posted is offensive please contact us. 

## Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Details of our subscribers and members are kept in secure areas of our server with encrypted passwords. Security of our site is controlled in part by our hosting service - 34SP. All activity on 4WebHelp.net is logged for security purposes. 

## Mailing lists

Any persons signing up for any of our in-house mailing lists are assured that we do not, under any circumstances sell, rent or otherwise redistribute our mailing lists to any other company. 

## Abuse/Inappropriate Communications

We reserve the right to forward abusive and inappropriate communications to the service providers of the originating communication and to relevant local, state, federal and international authorities. 

## Law enforcement

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request 

## Choice/Opt-Out

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  * You can send us an email via our contact form
  * Each email sent out contains a link at the end to allow for an easy removal from our mailing list

## Correct/Update

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  * Use the Profile section in our forums.
  * Email us via our contact form if you are unable to alter your own information.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with 4WebHelp.net, you can contact us via our contact form.
